{
    "id": "713f066c37f94a219b92235c278816e3",
    "title": "While And During | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met James ………………. my holiday in Japan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1bb747f94e54e9b8d2c9a0a35ebdca2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I injured my leg ……………….. playing football.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0c918b0646ea43899e9d2c72fd61cc18"
        },
        {
            "question": "I learnt French ……………. I was working in a museum in Paris.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ee522bcd1504481a4df6f2fc0336d20"
        },
        {
            "question": "It happened ……………. they were sleeping.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70d8882ad8654eb59eeb2abc6e74a2e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had a discussion ………………… the lunchbreak.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f372891f3a234d9d80b61be15860fff2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Something interesting happened ………………… my stay in Canada.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45b5dbb248094335b697d6e807c0eb12"
        },
        {
            "question": "People suffered a lot of hardships ……………. the floods.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4e8336a8a33844fd9c5ae971d9381fe3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I fell asleep …………….. I was watching the film.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bbd25fd2e8854c01ae44de9347377576"
        },
        {
            "question": "I fell asleep ……………. the service.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1bce4f94e3b54f85913225c5ca740be0"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. living in Rome, I met some really interesting people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "During"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f25a594fbbeb4d1c9c49e30fc55dee8a"
        }
    ]
}